couponsource.in 2016-05-17

# Privacy Policy - CouponSource

Privacy Policy & Opt Out

What information is collected?

When a customer orders something or registers on our website, certain information provided by the customer like the Name, Email –ID is stored in our database. Our website also gives an option to browse through our site without sharing any information. Our site is also used by Google as a third party vendor to serve ads. Google uses cookies specifically DART cookie to show ads based on the sites visited by the user. Users also have an option to opt out of use of DART cookie if they don’t want to receive ads based on the sites they have visited.

What do we use your information for?

We use this information for 3 basic purposes:

  1. Email –ID provided by you is used to send periodic emails or any offers which are ongoing. These will help you to get maximum advantage of our services.
  2. This information is also used to customize our website based on your liking such as if we know that you are looking for specific offers, our website will show them first based on your email id which you use while logging in.
  3. It also helps us to improve our website based on the feedback we receive from each of our customers.

How do we protect your information?

Lot of different security measures have been put in place to make sure that information provided and entered by you remains safe.

Do we use cookies?

Yes, we do use cookies to recognize your browser and personalize your experience based on what you were browsing previously. You also have an option to opt out of this service if you consider this as an intrusion of your privacy.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
None of the personal information provided by you is shared with any third party except the parties which help us in running our website. Even in such a scenario, lots of safeguards have been put in place to avoid any misuse of your personal data. Certain visitor information which is not personally identifiable is sometimes shared with other parties for various uses like marketing, advertising.

Third party links

There may be certain third party products or services being offered on our website. We will not be responsible or liable for any content being displayed through these third party sites but as we are responsible for our website, we would appreciate your feedback on any such third party links being offered on our website.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We comply with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act) and none of the products being offered on our website are directed towards children less than 13 years of age. Also, no information is captured for children less than 13 years on our website.

Use of Site Browsing History

By the use of website [www.couponsource.in](http://www.couponsource.in/), you are giving consent for us to store your browsing history which might be used for various purposes including displaying information to use based on your previous behavior. Some of this information might also be shared with trusted 3rd parties for various purposes like marketing, advertising. None of such information is personally identifiable but even then, if you want to opt out of such services, you can click on the Opt Out link and do so whenever you want.

Opt Out Page.

You can also setup your browser settings to reject 3rd party cookies. In addition, you can opt out of several similar programs by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative gateway opt-out site.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

Any changes being made to our privacy policy will be posted on our webpage

www.couponsource.in/
